Finding Aid for BMC Media Services records, 1851-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - I-L
    - Kaseta, Jennifer, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Kashman, Stacy, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Katz, Steven, Internal Medicine, Health Management and Policy, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Kaufer, Herbert, 1959; 1979; 1984 (Box 4)
    - Kauffman, Carol, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Kauffman, Kimberly, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 4)
    - Kawanishi, Hidenori, Internal Medicine, 1973 (Box 4)
    - Kay, Joseph, Pediatrics, undated (Box 4)
    - Kazajnian, Powel, Internal Medicine, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Kazanjian, Paul, Anesthesiology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Kazerooni, Ella, Radiology, undated (Box 4)
    - Kazmers, Irene, undated (Box 4)
    - Keane, Michael, Pulmonary, 1999; 2000 (Box 5)
    - Keegan, Catherine "Katy," Medical Genetics, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Kehoe, Amy, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Kelch, Robert P., 1970; undated (Box 5)
    - Keller, Evan, Gerontology, Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kelley(?)/Kelly?), Internal Medicine, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Kelly, (?), Internal Medicine, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Kelly, Howard A., undated (Box 5)
    - Kelly, Mable, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Kelsch, Robert C., Pediatrics, 1972; 1980; 1989; undated (Box 5)
    - Kemink, John, Otorhinolaryncology, 1982; undated (Box 5)
    - Kemp, Diane, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Kercher, Marley, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Kerlikowski, Albert C., 1940; 1949; undated (Box 5)
    - Kerr, Donald, Oral Surgery, undated (Box 5)
    - Kerry, Robert, 1959; 1971 (Box 5)
    - Kewman, Donald, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, Medical School Administration, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Khalidi, Nabil, Pharmacy, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Khater, Russell, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 5)
    - Kileny, Paul, Otolaryngology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Killian, Cheryl, Nursing, undated (Box 5)
    - Kim, (?), Internal Medicine, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Kindt, Glenn, Neurosurgery, 1961; 1969; 1978 (Box 5)
    - King, Beth, M Works, 1997 (Box 5)
    - King, Cheryl, Psychiatry, 1999 (Box 5)
    - King, Jeffrey, Orthopedic Surgery, 1999 (Box 5)
    - King, Steven, Oral Surgery, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Kiningham, Robert, Family Medicine, Sports Medicine, Medical School Administration, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kinter, Eileen, Nursing, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kirk, Chris, Surgery, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Kirschner, Denise, Microbiology and Immunology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kirsh, Marvin M., Thoracic Surgery, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Kissner, P., Internal Medicine, undated (Box 5)
    - Kizzer, Elizabeth, Population Fellow, School of Public Health (Box 5)
    - Klein, (?), B.E.P., undated (Box 5)
    - Kline, Phyllis, Anesthesiology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kling, 1985 (Box 5)
    - Klos, Donald M., Family Practice, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Knight, Bradley, Cardiology, Heart Care Program, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Knight, Karen, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Knopf, Theodore H., 1960 (Box 5)
    - Koch, Ellen, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Koeff, Steve, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Koenig, John, UMH Security Services, 1989; undated (Box 5)
    - Koenig, Ronald, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Koepke, George H., Physical Medicine, 1950; 1963; undated (Box 5)
    - Kohler, Rebecca, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kolars, Joseph, Gastroenterology, 1995; 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kolias, Ted, Cardiology, 1999; 2000 (Box 5)
    - Kolla, Srinivas, General Surgery,1999 (Box 5)
    - Konnack, John W., Urology, 1967; 1974; 1984 (Box 5)
    - Konzen, Ben, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Koo, Harry, Urology, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Kooi, Kenneth A., 1961; 1966 (Box 5)
    - Kopicki, Maria, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995; 1996 (Box 5)
    - Kostyo, Jack, Physiology, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Kovach, Julie, Cardiology, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Kozonis, Mary(?), 1998 (Box 5)
    - Kraft, Richard O., Surgery, 1954; 1960; undated (Box 5)
    - Krahn, Allen, Psychology, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Kramer, Michael, Primary Care, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Krause, Charles J., Otolaryngology, undated (Box 5)
    - Kretchmer, Norman, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 5)
    - Krone, Kathleen, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Kulik, Thomas, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Kumagai, Arno, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kunkel, Steven, Pathology, Rackham Graduate School, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Kurachi, (?), Internal Medicine, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Kwok, Roland, Biochemistry, 1998; 1999 (Box 5)
    - Kwon, Lik, see Martell, Lori, undated (Box 5)
    - Kyro, Kim, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Laetz, Ernest (includes wife), 1949; 1952; 1957; 1960; 1961; 1964 (Box 5)
    - undated (Box 5)
    - Lafleur, Lashawn, Neurology, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Lahorra, Joe, Thoracic Surgery, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Laidlaw, Ann, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Laing, Timothy, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Lambert, Matthew J. III, Surgery, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Lampe, Isadore, Radiology Therapy, 1959; 1972 (Box 5)
    - Lampman, Richard, Internal Medicine, 1974; 1989 (Box 5)
    - Lamprecht, Virginia, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Landis, Denise, Survival Flight, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Lane, Marie, Ophthalmology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Langenecker, Scott, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Lantz, Paula, School of Public Health, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Lapides, Jack W., Urology, 1951; 1973; 1978; undated (Box 5)
    - Lash, Robert, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Law, I., 1998 (Box 5)
    - Lawrence, Theodore, Radiation Oncology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Layton, Katherine, Pediatrics, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Leach, David (?) Medical School Administration, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Learned, David, Anesthesiology, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Leavey, Sean, Nephrology, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Leber, Steven "Steve", Neurology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Lebovic, Dan, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lechletner (Lusk), Sally, Nursing, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Ledger, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 5)
    - Lee, Andrew, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Lee, Cheryl, Urology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lee, Lisa, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Lefever, R. Dale, Family Practice, 1991 (Box 5)
    - Leichtman, Alan, Nephrology, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Leichtman, David A., 1975 (Box 5)
    - Leiden, Jeffrey, Cardiology, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Lenzo, Nat, Nuclear Medicine, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Leopold, Kathryn, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 5)
    - Letsos, Angie, Radiation Oncology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Levine, Allwyn J., 1971 (Box 5)
    - Levine, John, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Levine, Melvin, Biochemistry, 1954 (Box 5)
    - Levine, Myron, Human Genetics, undated (Box 5)
    - Levy, Kirk, CNL, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Lewis, (?), 1989 (Box 5)
    - Lewis, Earl, Rackham Graduate School, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lewis, Howard, Biochemistry, 1952 (Box 5)
    - Lewis, Ralph E., 1971 (Box 5)
    - Lewis, Toby, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Liang, Jersey, Gerontology, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Liberman-Lampear, Anita, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lichter, Allen, Radiation, Oncology, Medical School Administration, 1998; 1999; undated (Box 5)
    - Lichter, Paul, Ophthalmology, Kellogg Eye Center, 1978; 1998 (Box 5)
    - Lieberman, Richard, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997; 1999 (Box 5)
    - Lilja, James, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997; 1998 (Box 5)
    - Lim, Fred, 1994 (Box 5)
    - Lin, Ada, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lin, J., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Lin, Vivian, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Lin, X., School of Public Health, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Linabury, Diane, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Lindell, Dennis, Microbiology and Immunology, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Lindenauer, S. Martin, General Surgery, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Lindy, Robert M., 1970 (Box 5)
    - Linn, Andy, Social Work, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Lippman, Sheri, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2001 (Box 5)
    - LiPuma, John, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Liu, Hsi-Yen, Pediatrics, 1953; 1957; 1970; 1986 (Box 5)
    - Liu, Linda, General Surgery, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Liu, Rebecca, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995; 1999 (Box 5)
    - Livant, Donna, Radiation Oncology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lloyd, Thomas, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Lomax, Margaret, Otolaryngology, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Lombard, Warren Plimpton, Physiology, undated (Box 5)
    - Long, (?), Pediatrics, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Lopez, Manuel, Medical School Administration, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lorincz, Matthew, Neurology, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Losman, Eve, Emergency Medicine, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Louis, (?), Internal Medicine, undated (Box 5)
    - Louis, Dean, Orthopedics, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Loveland-Cherry, Carol, School of Nursing, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Lovell, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Lovell, Robert, Allergy, undated (Box 5)
    - Lowe, John B., Pathology, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Lozon, Marie, Emergency Medicine, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1999; 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lucchesi, Benedict R., Pharmacology, 1978; 2000 (Box 5)
    - Ludomirsky, Achi, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Luke, Barbara, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995; 1998 (Box 5)
    - Lydic, Ralph, Anesthesiology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Lynch, (?), 1953; 1954; 1956 (Box 5)
    - Lynch, (?), undated (Box 5)
    - Lynch, Joseph, Pulmonary, 1989; 2001 (Box 5)
    - Lynch, Peter, undated (Box 5)
    - Lyon, Greg, B.M.C., 1985 (Box 5)
  - M-O
    - MacDonald, Robert, Neurology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Mackenzie, (?), Surgery, undated (Box 5)
    - MacLean, Donald, Surgery, copy of late portrait, 1800s (Box 5)
    - Macomber, Marcia, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Madden, Michael, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Magee, John C., Transplant Surgery, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Magee, Kenneth R., Neurology, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Maher, K., 1998 (Box 5)
    - Maine, Gabriel, Immunology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Maino, John, Emergency Medicine, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Maio, Ronald, Emergency Medicine, 1999; 2001 (Box 5)
    - Malcolm, Sheree, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Malhotra, Jyoti, Pharmacology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Malinoff, Herbert, Internal Medicine, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Malkamaki, Dan, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Malow, Beth, Neurology, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Maltais, Catherine, Anesthesiology 1997 see Cupchak, Mary Jo, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Mancino, Laura, Immunology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Marcus, Shiela, Psychiatry, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Margolis, Philip M., Psychology, 1975; 1978 (Box 5)
    - Markel, Howard, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Marrengane, Ntombini, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Marrouici (?), Jacob, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Martel, William (includes wife), 1968; 1975; 1989; 1992; undated (Box 5)
    - Martell, Lori, undated (Box 5)
    - Martin, Claude, School of Business, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Martin, Dennis, Biomedical Research Core Facilities, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Martin, James N., Obstetrics and Diseases of Women and Children, circa 1890 (Box 5)
    - Martin, Julie, Internal Medicine, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Martinez, Internal Medicine, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Martini, T., Family Practice, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Martonyi, Csaba, Ophthalmology, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Martyn, Kristy, Nursing, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Marzano, David, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 5)
    - Matthews, Larry S., Orthopedic Surgery, 1997; undated (Box 5)
    - Matthews, Rowena, Chemistry, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Maxwell, James, undated (Box 5)
    - May, Joseph E., Allergy, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Mayne, Ken, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Mayo, William James, 1916 (Box 5)
    - McCarthy, Monica, Internal Medicine, 1997 (Box 6)
    - McClerking, Carolyn, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 6)
    - McCotter, Rollo, undated (Box 6)
    - McDermott, Mark, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 6)
    - McGillicuddy, John E., Neurosurgery, 1973; 1983 (Box 6)
    - McGraff, Paul, Credit Union, undated (Box 6)
    - McGuinness, Mary, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997 (Box 6)
    - McGuire, Edward, Urology, undated (Box 6)
    - McIntosh, Camille, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1996; undated (Box 6)
    - McLaughlin, Craig, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 6)
    - McLean, James, 1966 (Box 6)
    - McMahon, Laurence, Internal Medicine, 2000; 2001 (Box 6)
    - McNamara, James A., Dental, circa 1976 (Box 6)
    - McQuillan, Mark, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 6)
    - McRae, Thomas, Family Practice, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Meagher, (?), Cardiology, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Mecouch, John R., 1973 (Box 6)
    - Medina, Christopher, Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Meeks, Dwight D. (?), undated (Box 6)
    - Mehta, Maheshkumar, Anesthesiologist, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Mehta, Rajendra, Cardiology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Meisler, Miriam, Human Genetics, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Mellerick, Dervla, Pathology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Mendez, David, School of Public Health, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Menge, Alan, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 6)
    - Menon, Jairam K.M., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1973; 1992; undated (Box 6)
    - Merion, Robert, Transplant, undated (Box 6)
    - Merkel, Sandra "Sandy", Pediatric Pain Service, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Meso, Lisa, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Messana, Joseph, Nephrology, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Messina, Louis, Vascular Surgery, undated (Box 6)
    - Metzger, Bonnie, Nursing, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Metzger, Joseph, Physiology, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Meyer, Karen, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Meyers, Muriel C. (?), undated (Box 6)
    - Michalak, Darrin, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Midgley, A. Rees, Jr., Pathology, 1961; 1970 (Box 6)
    - Mikkelson, William M., Internal Medicine, 1968; 1975 (Box 6)
    - Mikol, Daniel, Neurology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Miller, (?) Communicative Disorders, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Miller, (?), Physical Medicine, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Audrey, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Carol, Neurosurgery, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Darla, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Miller, James Grier, Director of the Mental Health Research Institute, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Josef, Kresge Hearing and Research Institute, 1997; 2000 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Norman F. Jr. (includes family), Obstetrics and Gynecology 19561963, 1951; undated (Box 6)
    - Miller, Richard, Pathology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Sonya, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Minott, Sharon, Anesthesiology, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Mitchell, Beverly, Internal Medicine, Pharmacology, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Mitchell, Joyce, Rheumatology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Modinger, (?), Thoracic Surgery, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Montie, James, Urology, 1993; undated (Box 6)
    - Mooradian, Stephen, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Moore, (?) Family Practice, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Moore, Robert A., Psychiatry, undated (Box 6)
    - Morady, Fred, Cardiology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Morelock, Julie, Primary Care, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Morgan, Daniel, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 6)
    - Morley, George, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1959; 2001; undated (Box 6)
    - Morris, (?), undated (Box 6)
    - Morris, Penny, Alumni and Development, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Morrison, (?), 1954; undated (Box 6)
    - Mosca, Lori, Cardiology, 1998; 1999 (Box 6)
    - Mosca, Ralph, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Moscucci, Mauro, Cardiology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Mosely, Richard, Internal Medicine, 1996; 2000; 2001 (Box 6)
    - Mott, C. S., undated (Box 6)
    - Mountain, Kimberly, Psychology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Mountz, James, Nuclear Medicine, 1986 (Box 6)
    - Moyad, Mark, Urology, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Mozurkewich, Ellen, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Mueller, Kelly, Orthopedics, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Mulay, James, Immunology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Mulder, Ronald, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Mulholland, Michael, Surgery, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Munro, Hamish, Pediatric Anesthesiology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Murphy, (?), 1974 (Box 6)
    - Murray, Anthony, Dental Surgery 1998 see Glosser, Jeff, Dental Surgery, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Murtland, Terri, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 6)
    - Murugaiyan, Punitha, Neurology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - de Nancrde, Charles Beylard Gurard, Surgery, 1918; undated (Box 6)
    - Nabel, Elizabeth (Betsy), Immunology, 1996; 1997 (Box 6)
    - Nabel, Gary, Internal Medicine, Biological Chemistry, undated (Box 6)
    - Nagele, "Doc", Janitor, undated (Box 6)
    - Nagera, Perez, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Najerian, John S., 1991 (Box 6)
    - Nakada, T., Nuclear Medicine, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Napier, (?), 1969 (Box 6)
    - Nasonrin (?), Egor, Reproductive Science Program, undated (Box 6)
    - Nasr, Samya, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Nath, Sarah, Neurology, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Nathan, (?), Sports Medicine, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Naylor, Bernard, 1958 (Box 6)
    - Neal, Nathaniel, Internal Medicine, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Neal, Charles, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Neel, James V., Human Genetics, 1961; 1968; 1970; 1975; 1999 (Box 6)
    - Neidhart, Frederick C., Microbiology, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Nelson, Christine, Ophthalmology, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Nelson, Martha, Pediatrics 2000 also see Faix, Roger, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Nelson, Roger B., 1958 (Box 6)
    - Nemzek, Jean, Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Nesbit, Reed M., Surgery, 1958; 1959; 1968; undated (Box 6)
    - Nesse, Randolph, Psychology, undated (Box 6)
    - Neubig, Rick, Pharmacology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Newburgh, Louis H., circa 1948 (Box 6)
    - Newman, M. Haskell, Plastic Surgery, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Ngarmukos, Chardpraorn "Joy", Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Nicholson, Jane, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 6)
    - Nicklas, John, Internal Medicine, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Nigbor, Douglas, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Nostrant, Timothy, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Novy, Frederick, undated (Box 6)
    - Nugent, Clark, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 6)
    - Nungester, Walter J., Microbiology, undated (Box 6)
    - Nyachowe, Pascal, Surgery, 1996; 1999 (Box 6)
    - Nypaver, Michele, Emergency Medicine, Pediatrics, 1999 (Box 6)
    - O'Brien, John, Family Practice, 1979 (Box 6)
    - O'Campo, Flora, Oral Surgery, 1999 (Box 6)
    - O'Conner, (?), 1986 (Box 6)
    - O'Connor, J. Gerald(?), 1957; 1960 (Box 6)
    - O'Connor, Pat, Pediatrics, 1980 (Box 6)
    - O'Connor, Sylvester (?)(includes family), 1954; undated (Box 6)
    - O'Connor, Thomas P., Internal Medicine, 1989 (Box 6)
    - O'Leary, Mary Hope, Pediatrics, 1997 (Box 6)
    - O'Lone, (?), 1997 (Box 6)
    - O'Neal, Robert M., Plastic Surgery, 1969; 1984 (Box 6)
    - O'Shea, K. Sue, Cell and Developmental Biology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Oakley, Deborah, Nursing, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Oberman, Harold A., Pathology, 1958; 1971 (Box 6)
    - Odeku, E. Latunde, Neurosurgery, undated (Box 6)
    - Oelrich, Thomas, Anatomy, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Ogisu, Tatsuro, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Box 6 (cont.)Oh, Eugene, Radiology, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Ohye, Richard, Pediatric Cardiology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Ojo, Akinlolu, Nephrology, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Olanner, G., undated (Box 6)
    - Oliver, George, undated (Box 6)
    - Oliver, William J., Pediatrics, 1959; 1967; 1970; undated (Box 6)
    - Olsen, William R., Surgery, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Olson, (?), 1955 (Box 6)
    - Olson, Scott, Ovo Partners Inc., 2001 (Box 6)
    - Olson, William, Anesthesiology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Omenn, Gilbert, Internal Medicine, Human Genetics, and Public Health pictured with Larry Warren (see Warren, Larry), 1999 (Box 6)
    - Opipari, Anthony, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Opp, Mark, Anesthesiology, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Orlowski, Deborah, Human Resources, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Orrego, John, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Orringer, Kelly, Pediatrics, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Orringer, Mark, Thoracic Surgery, 1988; 1989; 1991; 1999; undated (Box 6)
    - Orsetti, Kym, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Orth, Kim, Biological Chemistry, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Osborne, Janet, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Osterholzer, John, Surgery, 199(?) (Box 6)
    - Osterling, Joseph, Urology, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Otteson, Deborah, Cell, Developmental and Neural Biology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Owsley, Joseph H., News and Information Services, 1970; 1971; 1983 (Box 6)
    - Owyang, Chung, Internal Medicine, 1995; 2000; 2001; undated (Box 6)
  - P-R
    - Padin, Cheryl, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 6)
    - Padmanabhan, Vasantha, Pediatrics, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Pahucki, Gena, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Palella, Thomas D., Internal Medicine, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Paluszny, Maria, Psychiatry, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Paradis, Cheryl, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Park, John, Urology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Parker, Peggy, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Parker, Walter R., 1932 (Box 6)
    - Parmacek, Michael, Cardiology, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Passaro, Erasmo, Neurology, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Patel, Paresh, Research Investigator at Molecular and Behavioral Neuroscience Institute, Psychiatry, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Patel, Smita, Radiology, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Patel, Sujata, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Patten, Bradley M., Anatomy, 1952 (Box 6)
    - Pawlik, Timothy, Surgery, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Payne, Anita, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Payne, Beverly C., 1966 (Box 6)
    - Pearlman, Mark, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Pearson, Deborah, Communicative Disorders, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Peck, Willis S., undated (Box 6)
    - Peet, Max (includes wife), 1946; 1965; undated (Box 6)
    - Peggs, James, Family Practice, 1999; 2001 (Box 6)
    - Pek, Sumer, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Pelegrini, Ivan, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Pender, Nola, Nursing, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Penner, John, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Pennington, Michele, Primary Care, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Perez, Violet, Family Medicine, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Perlow, Mark, Neurology, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Perucchini, Daniele, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Peschers, Ursula, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Peterson, (?), 1978 (Box 6)
    - Peterson, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Peterson, Reuben, Obstetrics and Gynecology, Director of University Hospital, 1931; undated (Box 6)
    - Petroff, Christy, Pediatrics, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Petty, Elizabeth, Internal Medicine, Human Genetics, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Petty, Ross E., Pediatrics, 1973; 1975 (Box 6)
    - Phan, Hannah, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Philleo, Cynthia, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Phillips, George, Pharmacy, 1970; 1973; undated (Box 6)
    - Phimphilai, Mattabhorn, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Phipps, Maureen, Obstetrics and Gynecology (Box 6)
    - Piehler, Lars, Biochemistry, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Pienta, Kenneth, Internal Medicine, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Pierce, Kathy, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Pierce, Penny, Nursing, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Pierson, Joanne, undated (Box 7)
    - Pilcavage, Christine, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Piper, Benjamin, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Pituch, Kenneth, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Plouff, L., Thomas, 1960; undated (Box 7)
    - Poli, Michelle (?), 2001 (Box 7)
    - Pollard, H. Marvin (includes wife), Internal Medicine, 1954; 1959; 1963; 1966; undated (Box 7)
    - Polley, Theodore, Surgery, 2000 (Box 7)